All who enter here...
Сюда входят
...are either jailers...
лишь тюремщики
...or prisoners.
и узники.
Which are you?
Кем будешь ты?
Neither. I'm merely a lost traveler.
Ни тем ни другим. Я всего лишь заплутавший странник.
What a spectacle! The Stellaron, the Ambrosial Arbor, the Disciples of Sanctus Medicus, the Lord Ravager...
Каков спектакль! Стелларон, Древо амброзии, Ученики Санктус Медикус, Лорд Опустошитель...
...a series of threats...
В череде опасностей
...that almost succeeded in diverting attention away...
почти удалось отвлечь внимание
...from the crucial question...
от краеугольного вопроса...
They who brought the Stellaron onto the Xianzhou...
Те, кто принёс Стелларон на Сяньчжоу...
What was their motive?
Что ими движило?
Will you surrender...
Сдашься ли ты,
...or do you require encouragement...
или получишь по заслугам,
...abomination of Yaoshi.
Мерзость Яоши?
General, my power does indeed stem from the Abundance.
Генерал, вы правы - источником моей силы является Изобилие.
But I'm the same as you.
Но я таков же, как вы.
We are both enemies of Yaoshi.
Мы оба враги Яоши.
That's right, Jing Yuan.
Так точно, генерал.
Stay out of our way.
Не стойте у нас на пути.
The revival of the Arbor is an omen. It's time for the Xianzhou to choose its next path.
Воскрешение Древа амброзии - дурной знак. Пришла пора для Сяньчжоу избрать новый Путь.
The Reignbow Arbiter, the Plagues Author, the Ruin Author...
Повелитель Небесной Дуги, Творительница Чумы, Творитель Руин...
This is a chess game between Aeons. If you don't stand with the winners, you stand to lose.
Это шахматная партия Эонов. Если ты не с победителями - ты проиграешь.
And this time,
На этот раз
We will put the Abundance in their grave.
мы уложим Изобилие в могилу.